bullocksbuzz.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy

This privacy policy was last updated: May 26, 2018.

## **Bullock’s Buzz Privacy Policy**

Bullock’s Buzz, https://bullocksbuzz.com/ (“Website”) is governed by the following privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”).

If you require more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at alainabethb (@) gmail (.)com.

At bullocksbuzz.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us, and we are committed to protecting it. This privacy policy explains what information of yours will be collected by Bullock’s Buzz when you use the Website, how the information will be used, and how you can control the collection, correction and/or deletion of that information.

Please be aware that we may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we do make changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this page and, in some cases, we may provide you with additional notice (such as by adding a statement to our website or by sending you an email). We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy whenever you access our site or otherwise interact with us in order to stay informed about our information, practices, and the ways you can help protect your privacy.

This statement only applies to this Website (Bullock’s Buzz at bullocksbuzz.com).

## Information We Collect

### Information You Provide to Us

This Website may collect information that you willingly provide directly to us such as your name or email address. For example, you may voluntarily submit information to the Website by leaving a comment, subscribing to a newsletter, participating in an event, survey, contest or promotion,or submitting a contact form.

The types of information that we may collect could include your name, email address (when you leave a comment), postal address and phone number (for shipping of prizes),  photo (when you use a Gravatar), preference or interest data, and any other information you choose to willingly provide.

### Information We Collect Automatically

#### Log Files

Like other Websites, bullocksbuzz.com automatically collects certain information about you and the device with which you access the Website through the use of log files. The information inside these log files may include a visitors internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks. This information is used to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information _are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable_.

### Information Collected by Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

This Website and our service providers may use various technologies to collect information, including cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on a hard drive or in a device’s memory that help us improve our website and your experience, see which areas and features of our website are popular, and count visits. Web beacons are electronic images that may be used in our Services or emails and help deliver cookies, count visits, and understand usage and campaign effectiveness. _For more information about cookies, and how to disable them, please see our[Cookie Policy](https://bullocksbuzz.com/cookie-policy/)_.

### Information Collected From Others

This website may receive information about you from other sources. For example, if you use a third-party software through the site, they may transfer information to us for fulfillment.

## How We Use the Information Collected

We may use the information about you or collected from you for various purposes, including:

  * to operate and maintain the Website;
  * to improve, maintain, and promote our products and services;
  * to send you promotional information, such as newsletters.  _If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email._
  * to communicate with you about products, services, surveys, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by our Website and others, and provide news and information we think will be of interest to you;
  * to send you administrative communications, such as administrative emails, confirmation emails, technical notices, updates on policies, or security alerts;
  * to respond to your comments, requests or inquiries;
  * to facilitate contests, sweepstakes and promotions, and process and deliver entries and rewards;
  * to monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our Services;
  * to track and measure advertising on the Website;
  * to protect, investigate, and deter against unauthorized or illegal activity, and
  * to carry out any other purpose for which the information was collected.

Bullock’s Buzz is in the United States of America and the information we collect is governed by American law. By accessing or using the Website or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the United States of America and other countries.

### Third Party Use of Information

This Website may share your information with third parties only when you _explicitly authorize_ us to share your information. Additionally, our Website uses third-party service providers (eg: MailChimp and Google Analytics) to service various aspects of our Website. Each third-party service provider’s use of your personal information is dictated by their respective privacy policies. Please see our [Cookie Policy](https://bullocksbuzz.com/cookie-policy/) for a full list of third-party services used on this Website.

### Social Sharing Features

This Website offers social sharing features and other integrated tools (such as the Facebook “Like” button and the Pinterest “Save” button), which let you share actions you take on our website with other media, and vice versa. Your use of such features enables the sharing of information with your friends or the public, depending on the settings you establish with the entity that provides the social sharing feature. For more information about the purpose and scope of data collection and processing in connection with social sharing features, please visit the privacy policies of the entities that provide these features.

### Advertising and Analytics Services Provided by Others

We may allow others to serve advertisements on our behalf across the Internet and to provide analytics services. These entities may use cookies, web beacons and other technologies to collect information about your use of this website and other websites, including your IP address, web browser, pages viewed, time spent on pages, links clicked and conversion information.

This information may be used by the Website and others to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, deliver advertising and content targeted to your interests on our Websites and better understand your online activity.

## Publically Visible Information

If you leave a comment, certain information you provide may be publicly visible. For example, Users may see your username, avatar, profile description and/or your website information. However, your email address will never be made available publicly.

## What Rights You Have Over Your Data

### Account Information

If you have left comments on this site, bullocksbuzz.com, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

**Opt-out** – you can easily opt-out of future email communications by following the unsubscribe links in our emails. You may also notify us at alainabethb@gmail.com to be removed from our mailing list.

**Access** – you may access the personal information we have about you by submitting a request to alainabethb@gmail.com.

**Amend** – you can contact us at alainabethb@gmail.com to amend or update your personal information.

**Forget** – in certain situations, you may request that we erase or forget your personal data. To do so, please submit a request to alainabethb@gmail.com.

## How we protect your information

This Website adopts the appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password and data stored on our Website.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We only provide articles and information.  
We never ask for credit card numbers.  
We use regular Malware Scanning.

## Sensitive Personal Information

At no time should you submit sensitive personal information to this Website. This includes your social security number, political opinions, information regarding race or ethnic origin, religious beliefs, health information, criminal background, or trade union memberships. If you elect to submit such information to us, it will be subject to this Privacy Policy.

## Children’s Information

The Website bullocksbuzz.com does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information from children under the age of 16. If a parent or guardian believes that the Website has personally identifiable information of a child under the age of 16 in its database, please contact us immediately at alainabethb@gmail.com and we will use our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require that commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. To learn more visit: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

  * Users can visit our site anonymously.
  * Once this Privacy Policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or, as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.
  * Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.
  * You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes by updates to this Privacy Policy page.
  * You can change your personal information by emailing us at alainabethb@gmail.com.

## Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (ex. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if you have visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

## Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from those images on the website.

## Contact Information

You may contact us at any time at alainabethb@gmail.com if you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy.
